Keep running along, watch as we pass by,
as we raise our flag, up high in the sky.
Alright,
here we go now, sailing through the
endless ocean, facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure nobody has
ever got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep believing in our
dreams, And let our heart lead the way!
Then once we got all the
others left is to go,
When we face the dark and stormy weather?
Keep the pace, we'll
link our hearts together!
Then I'm sure we'll make it through.
No matter what!
Keep running along, keep running along!
Start raising our flag as we journey on.
Though our chances are close to
none, We won't back down from anyone!
Let's start off the chase,
let's start off the chase!
Toward our own dreams,
while keeping the pace.
With a compass pointing to our goal,
We won't stop till we've
gone around the world!
Start me up!
Keep running along, keep running along!
And we'll never stop,
till we're at the top!
There's no way that we'll ever quit!
We'll keep heading for tomorrow.
Let's start up the chase,
let's start up the chase!
I see through your eyes
what we'll have to face.
All the memories we'll say in our hearts!
We'll never let them go.
Brand new world!
Let's start me up!
I must admit, I underestimated you!
I never imagined you could have made
it this far and by yourself no less!
Who says I'm by myself?
Couldn't have made it
here without my friends
and even if I could I wouldn't want to.
But you wouldn't understand that because
all you people think about it yourselves?
Soon my whole crew will be here
and we'll put an end to this!
Tempest Kick!
Shit!
Scary!
Don't let your guard down.
Yeah, right!
And stop doing stupid stuff.
Yes, sir!
Wait, what do you mean stupid stuff?
That's rude, you jerk!
No good.
My legs are too slippery for me to stand.
This power of yours sure is creepy.
Say whatever you like.
I know you're jealous.
Please, brag all you like.
It'll just make my
victory that much sweeter.
Oh, damn it.
What the hell was that?
Stupid deer gorilla going nuts I'll
deal with him when this mess is over I!
Still got to get the key
from that secretary lady?
Hey wait you dumb monster
stop stealing my thunder!
Let's crush him, Oimo!
Sounds good to me, Kashi!
Here we go!
Focus your attack on one
giant at a time, men!
Take him at Kashi's feet! Fire!
Good!
Now charge and bring him down!
Sounds like bad news out there.
Those giants have been holding back
the Marine Forces for a long time.
I'm sure they're wearing down.
Hey, hurry it up, will you?
Damn it.
I never thought a pirate
would make it so far.
This has turned into a real disaster.
Hey, Cape, this is your chief speaking.
What the hell are you
morons doing out there?
I got one of the straw
hats right on my heels.
Are you even listening to me?
You answer when I speak to you!
Wait!
You didn't press that button, did you?
No, this is the Golden Transponder Snail!
the silver transponder snail has received
a signal it's an emergency a Buster Call
has been requested under the authority of
admiral alkiji what's the location in his
lobby contact the five
vice admirals closest
to that location all things considered it
may be faster to reach
there from headquarters
how long there no more than 30 minutes
sir in that case prepare 10 battleships
for departure and inform the vice-admirals
of the situation make it quick yes sir a
Buster Call has been
requested the destination
is Enies Lobby repair 10 battleships for
sale immediately hello
hello what is it chief
oh now i get through this is the one i was
trying to use Not that it matters anymore.
There's no turning back now.
I push the button.
Of all things, it is done.
Triggered the Buster Call.
Did he say Buster Call? No way.
Is he supposed to be talking to us?
You have to cancel it right away!
Don't you realize what you've done?
Hey, that's Robin's voice!
Everyone is going to die!
Robin?
Cancel it?
Are you kidding?
Who do you think you're talking to?
You can't boss me around!
Why are they broadcasting this?
Hey, you! Don't move!
I can't! I'm tied up!
That's so what?
I mean, what's wrong with
the Buster Call anyway?
That's Chief Spandam
talking, I'm sure of it.
There's no reason for me
to get worked up over this.
Making that call was well within my power.
I'm the chief of Cypherpole
number nine, after all.
To ensure that your transfer goes over
smoothly, I requested a Buster Call.
There's not a thing
wrong with that who cares
if it's a little overkill
better safe than sorry.
It's a small price to
pay to make sure those
pirates get eliminated
you're a fool i told you.
Before that won't be
the end of it this is an
attack without mercy
without humanity i know.
That's the chief talking
but i don't recognize the
woman's voice the buster
cobble burn everything on.
The people, the buildings,
even the island itself!
It will sacrifice anything
and everything in its path!
The nightmare won't end
until nothing remains!
That's the power you're invoking!
If you had any idea what happened in Ohara
years ago, you would not be doing this!
The government is well aware
of the sacrifices involved.
That's how important this mission is.
Since Cutty Flam burned the blueprints to
Pluton, we can't afford to make a mistake.
You're the last hope we have
of reviving the ancient weapon.
We're talking about a military power
that can turn this whole era upside down.
Even if we have to sacrifice
a few thousand soldiers,
it's better than letting you
slip out of our hands again.
I know the consequences,
I just don't care.
Don't think of it as murder.
It's a sacrifice to protect the future.
And speaking of protecting the future, my
promotion is depending on this as well.
Hey, wait a second!
Can't we vote on this?
What does he mean by sacrifices?
Are they gonna kill us?
Think about this!
Human lives are at stake!
Allow me to remind you.
CP9 can kill in the name of justice.
Therefore, if we think 100 deaths
are needed to save 1,000 lives,
then we will kill those 100 people
immediately, without question.
For true justice, you must
be merciless at times.
Besides,
if those idiot soldiers
couldn't even stop a few
pirates from invading a
government base of this size,
they're better off dead anyway!
I think the line is still connected
on your transponder snail. Huh?
Oh, you gotta be freakin' kidding me!
Everyone heard all of that!
By the way, this is a
strong movie speaking.
Why would we believe that?
Everyone get off the island.
Hurry.
A Buster Call has been
invoked on Andy's lobby.
If you don't get away from
here immediately, you'll die.
Hey, don't tell them things
they don't need to know.
Well what should we do now I can't say
I'm happy but there's nothing we can do?
Yeah I should have seen it
coming with that idiot in charge!
Sounds like they're in some sort of
trouble the one in trouble here is me.
You poor miserable things all of your
hopes completely shattered I wouldn't
worry too much when it comes down to the
wire like this we always pull together!
Poor pirate boy, you must have been born
under a bad sign to have look like this.
But on the other hand, you probably
like it this way, don't ya?
We're gonna get hit with the buster!
Battleships are coming!
Get away from Enies Lobby!
I get that battleships are coming,
but why are the marines running away?
She said the island was going
to be burned to the ground.
Why would they burn down their own island?
I don't know.
Don't ask me.
Hey, if you're going to
run, at least untie us.
It's a Buster Call.
If you stay here, you'll die.
Bring as many ships as you
can and get ready to set sail.
The battleships could be here any second!
Guess they left us behind. Hey!
This is dangerous!
Get us out of here, dammit!
Are you kidding?
It's been dangerous ever since
we set foot on this place.
What about our big bro?
What's gonna happen to Franky?
There's no way we're leaving without him.
We'll wait as long as it takes.
The Straw Hats are coming, too.
Wait, wait, are you saying we should
just sit here and get blown up?
Come on, guys.
There's gotta be something we can do.
We can't afford to screw around anymore.
Then let's finish them off quick and get
to the Gates of Justice while we still can.
I just saw to something. Oh, yeah?
Like a way to get the handcuffs
off without any blood?
Or maybe a way to get out of here?
As a sword, you will be known
as the Great Blade Nose Storm.
That's kind of awesome,
but now's not the time!
I'M Chopper!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
Why couldn't you keep
your damn mouth shut?
Now the whole island's in a panic!
What if those pirates get away, huh?
You realize they're gonna
blame me for that, right?
Hey, wait a second!
If that was Robin talking,
then where is she?
Right behind these doors, of course.
As you seem to have surmised,
you'll have to go through me first.
I don't know.
Out of my way I'm not gonna let
you keep me from Robin any longer
say what you like This is the
end you'll never see her again
Seems we finally reached the climax
I'd better hurry.
If I stay here, I could die as well.
If you're gonna run, then
leave the key here with me.
Chouchou!
You must forgive me.
Alas, I fear the game must end now.
Hey, let me go!
At the very least, please
accept this parting gift.
Golden bubbles!
Damn it.
It's the same thing she did to Sanji.
I can't pick up the climate act.
I'm too slippery.
I can't even stand up.
Look at this mess. What did you do?
Well,
I admit this look doesn't exactly
do wonders for your curves,
but your skin is quite nice.
Although there is one catch.
Your already pathetic
strength has been cut in half.
I'd give up on the key if I were you.
Yeah, right. You wish.
Cool charge!
Stop wasting my time.
It's no use.
I call it mirage tempo.
I'm over here, by the way!
How dare you!
Don't toy with me!
They're all fakes.
Where did you go?
I'm right here
What is that?
She turned into a monster? Huh?
So you have Devil Fruit
powers as well, do you?
What a ditz!
Oh, my God.
That's it!
Ah!
It's a Buster Call!
The battleships are coming!
If we don't get moving, they're
gonna burn us to a crisp!
Run away!
I see.
So you have so-and-type
double-root powers, do you?
Are you dense?
I told you, that's not me!
But this isn't some random monster, is it?
Those are reindeer antlers.
And I'd recognize that cat anywhere.
But what happened?
Is that giant thing really, Chopper?
Even so, I'd never see a beast like this.
Boo-Boo!
Tempest!
Stop it!
Leave him alone!
Hey, Chopper, it's you, isn't it?
What's going on?
Did you do this?
Maybe he just doesn't recognize me now.
I must look strange.
You are Chopper, aren't you?
I was kidding. All right.
I didn't think you actually
turned into that thing.
Don't treat me like I'm a fool.
Chopper.
She ignored me so rude.
Chopper, what's wrong with you?
It's me, Nami! Look!
Stop it!
Why are you doing this?
Oh, no!
Sanchi's down there!
I don't know where that awful thing
wandered in from, but I'll make it pay!
Don't you lay a finger on him!
I won't let you hurt my friend!
What the heck happened to him?
This isn't good.
I need to find a way to stop him.
That thing is your friend? How amusing.
You pirates keep strange
company, don't you?
Chopper!
She ignored me again.
How rude can you get?
I'd love to have you take
care of that monster for me,
but I've been given an
order to eliminate you.
And time is running short.
Tempest!
Uh-oh!
I don't think I can dodge, but
my legs are slippery like this!
Huh?
I'm still okay?
One of my legs is back to normal.
But why?
Did I miss something?
It's wet.
It must have happened when
Chopper threw the bathtub.
Wait, I get it.
All I have to do is wash
the soap off with water.
Let's not be hasty.
Even if you can counter the
effects Of my golden bubbles with
water That doesn't mean I'm going
to stand by And let you do it?
Sheep cloud
Relaxing bubbles.
No problem!
This is nothing a little wind can't fix!
Now, side blow!
Damn it!
Oh, no!
My strength is...
Supple finger pistol!
My tag whip!
That was helpful. Helpful.
If you blow me away with
an attack like that,
then those annoying bubbles of yours
get blown away too, aren't you tough?
Well, if you like, I'll blow you
away until there's nothing left.
The forecast is cloudy.
This sure beats that
magic show stuff.
This thing used to do clouds
fighting with lightning again.
These clouds aren't
for lightning. They're?
Way too thin for that.
This time, I have something else in mind.
I see.
Damn, I should have known.
The forecast is rain.
Pool ball!
Pour down!
Rain temple!
And I work so hard.
How rude to wash everything away.
If your idea of nice is getting
my ass beat, then I'll pass.
Full charge!
Mirage tempo!
She's gone.
I've watched your every move.
I know your strengths.
And I know all your weaknesses as well.
What's happening?
Mirage Tempo!
Fight Morgana!